{
    "subject": "resource/Universidad_T\u00e9cnica_Estatal_de_Quevedo",
    "predicate": "ontology/foundingDate",
    "object": "1984-02-01",
    "human_readable": "The Universidad T\u00e9cnica Estatal de Quevedo was founded on February 1, 1984.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9656908512115479,
            "question": "When was the Universidad T\u00e9cnica Estatal de Quevedo founded?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.939556896686554,
            "question": "What is the founding date of the Universidad T\u00e9cnica Estatal de Quevedo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8997113108634949,
            "question": "On which day was the Universidad T\u00e9cnica Estatal de Quevedo established?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.832292377948761,
            "question": "How long ago was the Universidad T\u00e9cnica Estatal de Quevedo established?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7642672061920166,
            "question": "What month and year marked the beginning of the Universidad T\u00e9cnica Estatal de Quevedo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7482929825782776,
            "question": "In what year did the Universidad T\u00e9cnica Estatal de Quevedo begin operations?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7308979630470276,
            "question": "February 1st is associated with what event in Quevedo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7180504202842712,
            "question": "What significant educational institution was founded on February 1st, 1984?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6316648721694946,
            "question": "Is the Universidad T\u00e9cnica Estatal de Quevedo a relatively new university?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5667145252227783,
            "question": "What is the historical significance of February 1st in relation to education in Quevedo?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Universidad T\u00e9cnica Estatal de Quevedo was founded on February 1, 1984.",
            "html": "dbpedia_767_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is the Universidad T\u00e9cnica Estatal de Quevedo a relatively new university?",
            "html": "dbpedia_767_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What significant educational institution was founded on February 1st, 1984?",
            "html": "dbpedia_767_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=February 1st is associated with what event in Quevedo?",
            "html": "dbpedia_767_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_767_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_767_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_767_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_767_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_767_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_767_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_767_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_767_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_767_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_767_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe documents state that the Universidad T\u00e9cnica Estatal de Quevedo was founded in 1984 but they don't specify the exact date.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe documents mention that the Universidad T\u00e9cnica Estatal de Quevedo is \"Founded in 1984\" and also mention that the institution was awarded university status in 1984 (in one of the documents), but they do not specify a date of February 1, 1984."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents indicates that the Universidad T\u00e9cnica Estatal de Quevedo was founded in 1984, but there is no specific mention of February 1 as the exact date. Therefore, the statement specifying a founding date on February 1, 1984, cannot be confirmed based solely on the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Several sources state the founding year as 1984, without specifying a date.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The information provided states different foundation years for the university, including 1984 (points 1-3), 1976 (point 4), and no specific date or year mentioned in points 5-6.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information states that the Universidad T\u00e9cnica Estatal de Quevedo was established in 1984, but does not specify a particular date within that year. Therefore, February 1, 1984, cannot be confirmed as the exact founding date based on the provided information.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}